seven features that made Mr advik choose
ICICI Pro I protect return of Premium
with income benefit
option regular tax-free monthly income
from age 60 till policy
lapses up to 340% premiums returned
additional payout on diagnosis of 64
critical illnesses optional with just a
diagnostic
report up to two times coverage with
accidental death cover optional tax
savings of up to
54,600 rupees yearly and tax-free claim
payout and monthly income convenient
premium payment terms of 5 7 or 10 years
while you enjoy life cover for the
entire policy term freedom to continue
life cover and monthly income up to age
85 be wise like Mr advik invest in I cic
approve I protect return of Premium with
income benefit
now